dotnetfoundation.org 2016-11-11

# .NET Foundation - Privacy Policy

The .NET Foundation values your privacy. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized online experience. This Privacy Policy describes the conditions under which this Web site is being made available to you. The Privacy Policy discusses, among other things, how data obtained during your visit to this Web site may be collected and used. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using this Web site, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, please disconnect from this site and refrain from visiting the site in the future.

The .NET Foundation may decide at some point in the future, without advance notice, to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Web site, or materials obtained from the Web site, indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. The effective Privacy Policy will be posted on the Web site, and you should check upon every visit for any changes.

**Sites Covered by this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to all .NET Foundation-maintained Web sites, domains, information portals, and registries.

**Children’s Privacy**

.NET Foundation does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13, and .NET Foundation does not target its Web site to children.

**Links to Non-.NET Foundation Web Sites**

.NET Foundation’s Web site provides links to third-party Web sites for the convenience of our users. If you access those links, you will leave the .NET Foundation Web site. .NET Foundation does not control these third-party Web sites and does not represent that their policies and practices will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. For example, other Web sites may collect or use personal information about you in a manner different from that described in this document, so, you use other Web sites at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any Web site before submitting personal information.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Non-Personal Information**

Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not directly associated with a specific personal identity. .NET Foundation may collect and analyze non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the .NET Foundation Web site.

**Aggregate Information**

.NET Foundation may gather aggregate information, which refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and which cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the Web sites you visited just before and just after our site), the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. For example, when you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns and for purposes of system administration.

**Log Files**

Every time you request or download a file from the Web site, .NET Foundation may store data about these events and your IP address in a log file. .NET Foundation may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Web site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use or for other business purposes.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Our site may use a feature of your browser to set a “cookie” on your computer. Cookies are small packets of information that a Web site’s computer stores on your computer. .NET Foundation’s Web site can then read the cookies whenever you visit our site. We may use cookies in a number of ways, such as to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to deliver content specific to your interests and to track the pages you’ve visited. These cookies allow us to use the information we collect to customize your .NET Foundation experience so that your visit to our site is as relevant and as valuable to you as possible.

Most browser software can be set up to deal with cookies. You may modify your browser preferences to provide you with choices relating to cookies. If your preferences reject cookies, certain of the functions and conveniences of our Web site may not work properly, and you may be unable to use those .NET Foundation services that require registration in order to participate, or you will have to re-register each time you visit our site. .NET Foundation’s Web site also may use Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your use of our Web site and the Web sites of selected sponsors and advertisers, your use of special promotions or newsletters, and other activities. The information collected by Web beacons allows us to monitor how many people are using our Web site and selected sponsors’ sites; how many people open our emails; and for what purposes these actions are being taken. Our Web beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Web site or those of our sponsors. The .NET Foundation does not link non-personal information from Web beacons to personally identifiable information without your permission.

**Personal Information**

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. .NET Foundation uses personal information to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. On some .NET Foundation Web pages, you may be able to request information, subscribe to mailing lists, participate in online discussions, collaborate on documents, provide feedback, submit information into registries, register for events, apply for membership, or join technical committees or working groups. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, email address, user IDs, passwords, billing information, or other information.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

.NET Foundation may use non-personal data that is aggregated for reporting about .NET Foundation Web site usability, performance, and effectiveness. It may be used to improve the experience, usability, and content of the site.

**Information Sharing**

.NET Foundation does not sell, rent, or lease any individual’s personal information or lists of email addresses to anyone for marketing purposes, and we take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information. However, .NET Foundation reserves the right to supply any such information to any organization into which .NET Foundation may merge in the future or to which it may make any transfer in order to enable a third party to continue part or all of the .NET Foundation’s mission. We also reserve the right to release personal information to protect our systems or business, when we reasonably believe you to be in violation of our Terms of Use or if we reasonably believe you to have initiated or participated in any illegal activity. In addition, please be aware that in certain circumstances, .NET Foundation may be obligated to release your personal information pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or other orders.

In keeping with our open process, .NET Foundation may maintain publicly accessible archives for the vast majority of our activities. For example, posting an email message to any .NET Foundation-hosted mail list or discussion forum, subscribing to any .NET Foundation newsletter or registering for one of our public meetings may result in your email address becoming part of the publicly accessible archives.

Please remember that any information (including personal information) that you disclose in public areas of our Web site, such as forums, message boards, and news groups, becomes public information that others may collect, circulate, and use. Because we cannot and do not control the acts of others, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information about yourself or others in public forums such as these.

Personal information may be visible to persons outside your country of residence, including to persons in countries that your own country’s privacy laws and regulations deem deficient in ensuring an adequate level of protection for such information. If you are unsure whether this Privacy Policy is in conflict with applicable local rules, you should not submit your information. If you are located within the European Union, you should note that your information will be transferred to the United States, which is deemed by the European Union to have inadequate data protection. Nevertheless, in accordance with local laws implementing European Union Directive 95/46/EC of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (“EU Privacy Directive”), individuals located in countries outside of the United States of America who submit personal information do thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to its transfer to and/or storage in the United States of America.

If you do not want your personal information collected and used by .NET Foundation, please do not visit .NET Foundation’s Web site or apply for participation status.

**Security**

.NET Foundation makes reasonable commercial efforts to protect personal information by users of the Web site. Much of the personal information is used in conjunction with participation-level services such as collaboration and discussion, so some types of personal information such as your name, company affiliation, and email address will be visible to other .NET Foundation participators and to the public. .NET Foundation assumes no liability for the interception, alteration, or misuse of the information you provide. You alone are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please use care when you access this Web site and provide personal information.

**Opting Out**

From time to time .NET Foundation may email you electronic newsletters, announcements, surveys or other information. If you prefer not to receive any or all of these communications, you may opt out by following the directions provided within the electronic newsletters and announcements.

**Contacting Us**

Questions about this Privacy Policy? Contact us.
